Ashwini Wakchaure

PG Diploma in Advanced Computing

Self-motivated professional with more than three years of experience in a manufacturing environment. Seeking a career opportunity in a software company as a Full Stack Developer where I can use my extensive knowledge of programming languages and frameworks to develop efficient web applications.



ashwakchaure@gmail.com



9403918337



Pune, India



linkedin.com/in/ashwiniwakchaure-6a5b65161



github.com/ashwiniwakchaur e7777

SKILLS

NODE.JS

REACT.JS

JAVASCRIPT

EXPRESS.JS

MYSQL

HTML

MONGO DB

CSS

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Listening music

Reading

Travelling

EDUCATION

Post Graduation Diploma in Advanced Computing

Centre for Development of Advanced Computing

09/2022 - 03/2023

CCEE: A Grade

Project

Project - Hospital Management System

Bachelors in Mechanical Engineering

Sinhagad Academy of Engineering

06/2015 - 06/2018

75.06%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Process Automation Specialist

Infosys BPM Ltd

11/2021 - 06/2022

11/2021-00/2022

Pune

Work and responsibilities

Worked on Generation of Purchase Orders & timely issuance of POs to Vendors, follow-up for

order confirmation, and co-ordination for on-time payment to suppliers

- Handled all P2P activities and handles the PO related queries
- Handled overseas Suppliers, tracking & maintaining system

Purchase Executive

Tata Motors Ltd

12/2018 - 11/2021

Pune

Work and responsibilities

- Interpreted engineering drawings, part lists and volume of materials to make informed purchase decisions
- Analyzed vendors and suppliers to select the most suitable to deliver high-quality products at competitive pricing
- Implemented alternate sourcing of static suppliers through sourcing with another suppliers
- Developed, implemented, and drove purchase strategies to meet cost savings targets, planned supplier's capacity to meet production requirements
- Liaised with vendors and suppliers on delivery schedule to achieve on-time delivery, raw material indexing

ACHIEVEMENTS

Received applause for early self enablement

□ Infosys BPM Ltd

Received appreciation and kudos for driving execution

□ Tata Motors Ltd